CONNOR FLETCHER

Flat 21, 20 Knyveton Road
Bournemouth
BH1 3QS
07592 498734
cfletcher.programmer@hotmail.com
cfletcher.devilshell.uk



PERSONAL ATTRIBUTE

I am a 23 year old, reliable, hardworking, friendly team player. I build up my experience and knowledge by tackling every task given and carrying them out to the best of my abilities. I thrive on challenge and problem solving, focusing on my objectives to completion.



EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science (hons) 2.1 in Games Programming | Bournemouth University

2014 - 2017

Foundation Degree (D)istinction*D*D in Games Development | Somerset College of Arts and Technology

2012 - 2014

Additional Education - Functional Skills Level 2, Employability Skills Level 2

GCSE | The Taunton Academy 2007 – 2012



EXPERIENCE

Games Design & Games Software Engineering Demonstrator | Bournemouth University

AUGUST 2018 - PRESENT

Jobs included: Teaching students to code in C++ (with OpenGL 4.x Core and SDL 2.0) and C# with Unity 2017.4.5. Teaching students the core principles of Games Design with regards to Meaningful Play, Core Dynamics and Frameworks.

Sales Team Leader | Maplin Electronics JULY 2017 – JULY 2018

Jobs included: Working with stock management and rotation. Assisted customers who needed help. Always worked to a target and consistently hit them. Opening and running the store. Managing the team.



SKILLS

- Specialise in C++ and C#.
- Proficient in a variety of other languages
- Well versed in Version Control on a number of different systems
- Able to work through multiple processes of games development such as: Graphics, Physics, Game play etc.
- Knowledge in engine architecture and usage (Unity and Unreal Engine).



RESEARCH PAPERS

Virtual Reality Ear Training System: A study on Spatialised Audio in Interval Recognition

06/09/2019 (ACCEPTED)

This research project was based around musical training using the tones of musical notes using a VR environment. By using the built-in 3D audio panning within Unity 2017.4.5, tests could be done to see if the use of panning audio compared to stereo enhances the training experience or has a null affect.



REFERENCES

References provided upon request!